P-U-N-J ain't dead, it just smells that way in bed.
They said it died in 79, with the mohawk mullets and the cheap-ass wine.
Then again, in 88, when the Legos came to seal its fame.
Plunked his dad on his bunk, stuck in the fan with a gasket sunk.
Metal bed dirt to sticker trunks, stuffed with pink bread from the bottom bunk.
Hey, hey, hey, long.
Never give up.
Remember when the scene got clean?
Sanitized with corporate sheen But Bunk survived in basement shows And fifth-story chat, it's full of holes So paint your nails with gasoline Left Furnic down, you know the scene The world keeps sucking more each day So Bunk ain't dead, it just won't pay Bunk is dead, long live Bunk Stuffed in a vein where the gas tanks suck
Now go back to just diggin' slugs Stuff with big butts from the bottom bunks Hey, hey, bong this fuck Hey, hey, never give up Dis-ter-gate